Yaoyao
Sun Ming
Sorry to bother you.
Ms. Gu Ting.
My condolences.
The police need your cooperation for a statement
to help us understand the situation.
I understand you now.
She and Yaoyao
are exactly alike.
But
I know what to do.
Take this.
It can save your life when it counts.
We pulled surveillance footage from multiple areas.
After comparing them,
we finally confirmed
that the one who initially kidnapped Gu Ting
was Grass Snake.
But Gu Ting explicitly stated
that the masked suspect
was not Grass Snake.
So,
Grass Snake was silenced.
I suspect
Yan Li squeezed the last drop of value from Grass Snake,
then discarded him.
What about evidence at the scene?
Completely clean.
The suspect left no biological traces.
With Grass Snake dead,
his successor
is highly likely to be Bro Liu.
I will go find Bro Liu.
No, you cannot.
Bro Liu is cunning and paranoid.
He will definitely suspect you.
It is too dangerous.
You need to find a way to lure him out,
and let us arrest him.
No.
Their methods are too unpredictable.
It is easy to tip off the enemy.
Most importantly,
he is the only way to find evidence of Yan Li's crimes.
Bro Liu probably does not even know
where Yan Li's real hideout is.
How does it feel sitting in Grass Snake's seat?
Sir.
We all work for you.
We always look out for you, Sir.
I told you to get a few guys to keep watch.
Why did you run off by yourself?
No, no.
Sir.
I just figured I'd patrol a bit further out that day.
I didn't expect that right after I left,
the police would show up.
Really.
It's true.
I will believe you for now.
As long as you stay loyal to me,
I will not treat you badly.
Yes, I will be absolutely loyal.
Remember this.
No matter what it is,
you can only take what I give you.
Do not try to be clever.
Otherwise,
I will send you
to partner up with Grass Snake.
Understood.
Also,
starting today,
you are in charge of this company.
The monthly quota
is at least five million.
My commission
needs to be
ten percent higher than before.
Any objections?
No objections.
Thank you, Sir.
Good.
Five million?
With the cops watching so closely,
how am I supposed to hit five million?
That's a pipe dream.
Hello?
Brother Liu!
I finally got out of that detention center.
I heard you got promoted.
Can I come work for you?
What's wrong, Brother Liu?
Is it a bad time?
No, it's a great time.
I'll send someone to pick you up.
Great, Brother Liu.
I'll be waiting.
Brother Liu!
What's going on here?
Opening a new company,
making it boom.
It's also to avoid suspicion.
Nothing good ever happens when I run into you.
You really had the nerve to show up.
Brother Liu.
I spent seven whole days in the detention center.
How can I make it right?
You don't even believe me.
How are you gonna make it right?
I met an older guy inside for drunk driving this time.
He's got deep pockets.
He's very confident in himself.
Has millions ready to invest.
Seriously?
Of course it's true.
Brother Liu,
you just took over.
You definitely need results, right?
Let your little bro help you out.
Brother Liu, don't hesitate.
There are already plenty of financial managers
targeting this guy,
getting ready to scam him.
We gotta hurry.
Little bro,
it's not that I don't believe you.
Someone complained to me that you're no good.
Don't be offended.
Brother Liu,
I'm actually
not offended at all.
It's nothing.
It's just that if this deal works out,
about my cut...
bump it up a bit.
No sweat.
As long as it goes through,
you'll get your fair share.
Thank you, Brother Liu.
Brains and brawn
fits Brother Liu's vibe perfectly.
Good eye.
Dye your hair,
and I'll make you a master.
Really?
I've always wanted to dye my hair blond.
Know a bit about fashion.
Hello.
Send me a personnel list for your new company
and their contact info.
The more detailed, the better.
Okay, okay.
Brother Liu,
we gave that guy a little taste a few days ago,
and he took the bait.
Says he wants to meet the Financial Master now.
What should we do?
Call him!
Hurry up.
What if someone else scams him first?
Hurry!
Oh, got it.
Hello?
Boss Gu.
Master Liu is sitting right next to me.
Ask him whatever you want to know.
Hello, Grandmaster Liu.
I wouldn't call myself a grandmaster.
Just call me Master Liu.
Hello, Master Liu.
Master Liu,
Boss Gu here is a beginner.
He wants to invest,
but doesn't have the channels.
So he wanted to ask for your advice.
Investing as a beginner
carries a lot of risk.
I suggest you wait and see.
Come on.
Master Liu,
Boss Gu is really sincere.
Do it for my sake,
and help him out.
Yeah, yeah.
So,
what kind of investment is Boss Gu looking for?
I heard from Little Li
that your wealth management returns are quite stable.
I want to give it a try.
It's like this, Boss Gu.
Our investment projects
are only open to our VIPs.
Then how can I become a VIP member?
Boss Gu, our VIP screening process
is extremely strict.
That's no problem.
Can I apply?
Come on, Grandmaster Liu.
Boss Gu is my friend.
If it comes down to it,
I'll vouch for him.
All right.
For Little Li's sake,
I'll make an exception for you.
Boss Gu can become our VIP.
But we have to sign a contract,
so Boss Gu doesn't skip out on our cut once he makes a profit.
Right?
That won't happen.
I won't back out on what I owe.
Don't worry.
Wait a moment.
Boss Gu is so straightforward!
How much is Boss Gu preparing to invest?
As for me,
I'm very cautious with investments.
I'll start with two million to test the waters.
Is that okay?
Two million?
Two million...
I've never even seen that much money.
No problem.
Your two million
will go into our Sure Win Plan.
I can guarantee
your return will be over 30 percent.
30 percent?
That sounds great!
How about this?
Why don't we have morning tea together
and sign the contract in person?
Master Liu, does that work for you?
What do we do about this?
What do we do?
No problem.
Send me an address,
and I'll see you there.
Sure thing, no problem.
Wait for my message.
Two million...
We're rich!
Brother Liu,
you need to dye your hair back.
Why?
It's burgundy right now,
not true red.
We're about to be loaded!
Loaded!
Loaded indeed.
Change it back.
Little brother,
it's not that I don't trust you.
You have too much of a track record.
Stay right here.
Wait for my triumphant return.
Let's go.
Let's go dye my hair.
Seven, eight, nine.
You guys go find somewhere to hang out for a bit.
I have some business to attend to.
Damn, Sun Ming.